for ICC Bank it is clearly visible that
uh these numbers and what they've done
in last two quarters clearly they've
they now
enjoying benefits of a mega
restructuring and a new business uh
cycle comeback on the Kasa front numbers
are strong on the NS I think things
would head higher the subsidaries are
firing full cylinders so while you would
always consider few years ago ICI Bank
as a bet on the cop sector I think now
given where the retail market share is
where Kasa is IC bank I think will enjoy
a premium positioning for its retail and
its subsidary and the way some of the
subsidiaries in a sense have made a
comeback so if you look at the headro
you've always positioned kotak Mahindra
bank right at the top followed by HDFC
bank and then it used to be a tossup
between access bank and IC bank I
genuinely feel that IC bank has Headroom
left to catch up which means that in the
near term there could be in case for ICC
bank now to outperform both cak and HDFC
Bank given that how the valuation headro
is limited business is coming back
things have stabilized the Kasa is
looking solid and the subsidaries of
firing full cylinders you know AA the
subsidiaries all of them now uh are
sizable businesses in their own category
whether it is IC Lombard whether it is
ICI uh ICI life insurance business
uh the size I think for ICA securities
also is a very large one I will not be
surprised that within next 12 18 months
if ICICI potential AMC also goes public
so they're getting their restructuring I
think has really benefited them the
change of guard which happened after
Chanda coach's exit I think has worked
for IC Bank shareholders uh so there is
a bit of a valuation catch up which it
could do considering that it is still
trading at a very fairly largest
discount to hdf bank and kotak Mahindra
bank and also typically you want to be
with a bank which is a play on bhat now
uh you know unlike Aisha let's say kotak
Mahindra bank which is a great play on a
balance sheet which is a great play on
technology ICC Bank in a sense is a
complete play on bhat because if you buy
the stock now you get insurance you get
uh General Insurance you get broking you
pretty much are getting all the business
verticals which are there in the
financial space per se